hi guys sorry we're a little late every
time you I I logged out of Twitter and
it logged I wasn't even like leave them
in there for like a mask on we need some
air thank you Eric I know it's very
smart so exciting
Oh feels like so I guess yeah I guess
like let's talk in the order of what's
exciting okay what's the most exciting
ones there's this walkway here that's
kind of new it's actually really
dangerous and there's lots of cars that
are like accidentally crashing over the
crosswalk okay I'm sorry that must have
like made people feel really freakin
with 0.546 coming out hopefully tonight
and it's gonna bring good stuff for
users so most important thing is well
okay so there is like a stylistic update
there's a new setting asking about the
most common thing which is for everybody
calibration algorithm is always active
on the road yeah this turn is so
dangerous
settings look great thank you Andrew
okay
it's a takeout is it still green either
oh it's still bad okay so the other
thing that are cool is we changed the
standard G offsetting so if you ever
known that stop doing zero zero zero
zero four zero setting actually do zero
one one one one of us what this do is
it's gonna put back the camera stock for
anything that is not needed by open pile
to drive the car so if you have like one
of the new one does that have Auto high
beams or all the other features they are
gonna work because there we are gonna
pass them through using the panda so you
you will be alerted when you turn on the
car you will receive an alert if you
have like the GF back to the old
configuration which is like zero zero
zero zero yeah where he would attack you
alert you to go to the correct settings
exactly will tell you the new
geographies change actually you can do a
live type of state probably Apple oh so
if I change the wrong switch back we're
good live same thing works on Toyota two
Toyota's great doing these because I
call the Toyotas have how to high beam
features people were we're missing it
their only problem with the Toyota is
they're you
the 120 ohm resistor to terminate the
can the camera can mm-hmm so we started
to ship the 120 ohm resistor you
probably received if you receive the
giraffe we know that would be like the
next step the next step would be do
everything entirely like in software
it's a good question
so we are gonna keep the key you're
gonna stay like physically on this
setting before they wonder like 0 1 1 1
and then of your software you can switch
between stock and non stop by since we
so you oughta cheer after don't support
these configuration because they don't
have the resistor we don't want to fire
people yeah we don't want to force
people want to be that compatible not
airsoft people that don't have the
resistor so we're thinking about it but
definitely yes there and that's where
we're going now is no more switches
giraffes are kind of this is the first
step Oh Danna this angle is amazing yeah
we're totally give you guys news about
okay so other stuff exposed table but
that was already merged into the main
evidence so you guys are not like last
calculation public for sure
well the kid they honed the acceleration
is still better again everybody
complained because he wasn't fast enough
then we made it faster but until you saw
their problems I think we release we
have the best of both worlds so no
drawbacks but find acceleration so you
who said private forever and then when
is this release coming they try to ride
tonight I need a stir
like all the cars but probably tonight
yeah
so what are the questions this
acceleration limited by Honda well so
what allows a pretty good acceleration I
would say it's limited by yowza
like we use less than acceleration and
actually all that allows because it's
very abrupt of the way that the
acceleration is done by Yolanda so we
have kind of like how to limit it to any
update so the car will not try and take
exits we've been pretty good about that
for the pad since like the previous
release I mean we kind of disabled exits
in a way right left biased we I think
he's gonna I mean like new mothers are
gonna be better I'm back there I
wouldn't say that these model is gonna
be particularly bad there but like yes
like once we starting to create more
from the maps and this is gonna become
like very soon car for sure yeah the
speed limit is like a first intro of
tying the maps in well because like so
you'll need to do is do we drive like we
drive guys don't try to change your
settings that's specially Toyota doesn't
work
now one does like a little more amenable
of it but you weren't able to engage
though because like when you switch the
gene off like me we try you have some
fault there's like double features on
this release no you don't need you don't
need actually okay so for these are
these you don't vote for them like this
in the future so to get like this people
ladies which is not it is but it's gonna
be like in the next up did you have a
gamepad is gonna work back there yeah
because we're going to be watching
yummers up here external antenna gives
you more integrated features like this
little case so there is there's two
things one thing is like how do we take
advantage of like maps like low
resolution maps if this is something
that we started right now this is
actually not using any of HD maps but
the other thing that we wanted oh by the
end of the year is a start but is HD
maps and we try to have some like
limited our HD maps released and gave
basically the idea of scalability like
as we get more data how can we stand the
HD maps Aria coverage and so then it
will become just a bit of a scalability
problem but I give the ear at least like
portion of
California from the Bay Area's the
corner by um seats
yes we're building the right now so
those are existing GPU CPU D sp3 sp3 the
DSP calm yeah we used this before or D
some part of the ungrateful corpse
well this seems like it's good a time as
any to announce the fact you know where
to car we're periscoping we're
self-driving and we're in San Francisco
but this is also gonna be true through
the states of California New Mexico
Arizona Texas and that's it is there one
more thing
well Louisiana but we're not wasting a
minha we just want to party Louisiana we
are we are officially announcing the
self-driving car tour today did we
already announced this I think we may
have done it again we're doing it again
and we're coming down south we're going
to LA we're going to Phoenix we're going
to Dallas and we're hosting meetups and
we're going to have exclusive slag that
you can only get on the tour we're also
gonna have the common mobile shop
and can we announce the crew or is that
gonna be a surprise
we can announce we can a salsa team
the team that's going on this fabulous
road trip is gonna be Eddie
Ricardo Harold and myself in person
which a lot of people do so get in line
it's gonna be very exciting
oh I forgot to announce one more meetup
in San Francisco
our first ever Bay Area meetup which is
really ridiculous that's taken us this
long it's going to be yeah you can get a
haircut at the meetup I'll bring my
[Music]
that's fine actually if I fight if I'm
legally allowed to do that and say it's
I'll totally give you guys oh yeah we
are having a San Francisco Meetup and
it's gonna be December 12th it's gonna
be at the Airbnb headquarters to Airbnb
for hosting us mark mark LV and Mark
Hill BK December 12 and think at 6 p.m.
we'll announce we'll have like a medium
post with all of these links it's
practical to sign up for the SF beat up
because of Airbnb security policies they
just have to get you I was like an event
right or some prey it's pretty fancy
so yeah they'll be food we'll make sure
there's food on all of our meetups will
like bring pizza any good maybe some
Arby's apple turnovers yeah because
we're also looking for sponsorships with
a self-driving car tour so are these if
you're listening we need our be a
channel we need gasoline peace it go
will be basically come six out goes yeah
if I could pick any gas company be 76
they're the most stylish me I'll get you
got haircuts no progress
I'll bring your clippers but seriously
we are looking for a sponsor the yeah
this is exciting news so we'll have more
more information about all these places
and locations the location that is like
almost for certain right now is we're
hoping to do it at the fuse makerspace
in I believe that thing's an Albuquerque
it looks pretty fancy and hopefully the
Dallas makerspace in Dallas there are
nonprofit and so they're hesitant to
allow us to come but I was like that
ceiling
P an express sponsor yet we're so DIY
like all of our giraffes or open sores
yeah you know that's gonna remain in
effect yeah we're open sourcing some new
tools oh yeah in the next few very
important so we're gonna open a pilot
we're gonna open source it because we
figured that it's not the best way to
the communities we physically community
you know in our same spot the way that
we develop should be the way that the
community develops here or there cam so
we're gonna open source a lot of our
attention open up our tools maybe you've
heard of unlocker that's a we might
mentioned sometimes on these scopes
that's a tool be opening soon yeah
[Music]
yeah so we're seing tools people are
excited sourcing tools like you know
this is what you need like some social
drive to make tools and products good
like if they're not open if they just
remain internal they're not going to be
very good for us to use and it's just
better when you open it yeah it drives
you to it forces you it puts you in the
spotlights you they have to look good
yeah exactly
so no more excuse - Aiza yeah you're f
tucson Peterson like don't make it
better for us and obviously for you guys
those policy expands toys as well yeah I
mean along with tools you know tools
should be you know we don't use too many
comments because comments get outdated
well code does not but like you know
they'll be documentation long or not
because la maker spaces are part of
contents
message me on slack about where your
office is because that could be great
Irvine California we're not coming to
San Mateo but we are going to be Airbnb
offices are in soma so so ma San Mateo
that's pretty food right now we're
driving my coma it's like whole motto so
Morgan kept going down our living that's
what they said that's what they said
people just die are you guys getting
that that's insane
that's cold they have a heart and stuff
[Music]
what else yeah we're saying to explore
the great southwest of the United States
yeah if anyone wants to you know join us
for some of the torrent for a raid where
we line up across the highway
yeah HD mmm the door is really great for
people who came out last year was a
great time and if you help us organize
we give you some free swag which is also
an even better time yeah
any other questions what's going on in
there
76 people are still here is there a blog
post on the update for the release week
there's like a github release notes
Japanese no as you know we're about
delay um likely like a I don't know
downtown LA LA is huge is something yeah
I was like map looks like hosting two
hours skin from one end to the other but
we'll let you guys know I wanted to be I
wanted to be
their accounting actually another good
thing about that is we are now
supporting the and there's GM giraffe I
saw zona as a lesser and support that
you ladies I'm actually selling the GM
tear yeah there's a GM giraffe out there
so you know as I'm working out of the
box by the Jeff here yuppie tasarov's
been really no other ports searched so
the noise emerged but it's like a yeah
we don't we don't we're not that
comfortable like officially supporting
these cars that we don't like have
access to kinda makes us nervous but
there's enough people doing it well
there's enough people doing it
definitely and we are a beautiful that
receiver you like the safety seems
pretty good
good job so we paid out the man yeah is
this now mr. diets for me to sponsor
there's a GM Tesla community ports
jun-tae we are teaching support these
internally here supported you guys
really good this it said the Hyundai is
like any of your driving on 2019 Carson
like I said any of you you've seen the
open pilot on 2019 cars like to know
because we would like to lease them into
their EP and actually we don't have any
really turned about many many people
using it but maybe I'm sure you guys out
there you see t6 was on point five five
with Subarus do you need three pandas
five full on a Cadillac picks up
everywhere yeah we find us
you need pandas and like some special
connectors well yeah you need like a
four yeah it's kind of a it's pretty
janky we can open source it I can have
like Nick touch it up and release it
it's kind of complicated to use but but
yeah it's got a complicated like there's
pandas running doing some forwarding
that aren't connected today eons it's
like they can't evacuate campus
yeah but it is a bit like the Cadillac
actuators are so nice like open quite a
lot of kind of expanding well it's
really good I think Greg uses no no he's
been using stock yeah
turning out to be exactly the same as LS
600 2008 to 2015 is it a Lexington
thanks yeah wow so complex but will be
needed for 2020 escalate
2000 there's gonna have super cruise on
this they should they should have super
cruise on more cards like it's it's
requires like you should have a huge
metallic cover like double but it on
that see you that there's like they cost
check each other it's really over
engineer there's like flexpay cameras a
lot of things to be going on other for
other luxury it's just complicated
what's really like the like you know pmw
or like somehow DS uses the Cadillac
uses it but like there's just not a lot
of support for it on like hardware wise
or driver-wise whatever
so it's never gonna be it's never
actually gonna overtake us my Prudential
but yeah like they own the mold they
have like HD maps on the car they're
able to ship updates to the maps but
there's the system itself what we really
need to find before the road trip is the
stabilizer because that's gonna make
these pairs go so much better yeah I
think
the rumors on George's that he's still
in the closet closet
he told us like he's living he's going
to try living be our hundred has el Casa
nice to see bunnies to pandas so far
what is that what about Toyota pedal
support so what is a toilet pedal well
we got this we got the pedal I think
we're gonna try it depending how good it
works so we might actually merge in the
code that supports the like we will
never like a feature you support the
fill it up
but we can merge in the code that makes
it compatible like Honda so we will see
later I don't remember who sent to us
but I guess we tried you need the pedal
for stopping there no yes well there are
certain Toyota's where they don't do
stop and go but we talking pilot you can
do stop and go but they did majority of
Toyotas they cannot do something go you
still cannot retreat open Toyota rav4
yes no not for I believe you can we
should put in our and we don't have any
cars with a pedal now that's right go
for seven go oh yeah the Acura was the
only car we had with the pedal and
that's long yeah you don't need on this
Civic are you do beyond telling recorder
to look straight ahead yeah yeah it
won't be bit you unless the cars movie
if you're not if you're just stopped
it'll just kind of remind you
driver monitoring is really good it's
really good can you change follow
distance now on Honda Civic winter zero
point five point six no no we don't do
that that's not a thing don't change I
don't know you can do that on Toyota's I
think but not with open pipe but like
with the stock system I don't know it's
not really something you want now to do
we just puts the optimal distance what
is the offset on the eon in that in this
car in this cross o
Indus can respond to like about like
whatever these are coded like six
centimeter maybe but why yeah the camera
I'll sit with respect to the center sure
if that's what they are asking still got
68 good users we really used this mount
remember that remember we mounted a
GoPro on this like ball joint we can't
find the other side though oh really
but that's really we need to mount a
camp well the greatest is when there's a
rear view mirror and you can get like
the fully yeah oh sorry
we have flipped giraffes oh I think
being added to the store next week we
got flipped giraffe so that's like
Odyssey not sure what other cars on its
also nineteen cars engine has a nineteen
like the this connector on the camera is
flipped around like on this one it goes
the tab is on the bottom and on summits
on the top I don't know I would like so
someone made I think someone
did a flip of it first and now we have a
production version we just got like 100
I think manis yes I'm Nick we'll be
adding that to the store next week add
to the many many jurat that we have
yeah that's more news we got hoodies are
in stock you need a hoodie chili great
buddies are great they have they got a
white string on a black background
yeah someone had a gray in the SoCal
meetup picture there's one had a gray
hoodie with a black comma it looked
pretty good I don't know who that was
yeah but so cool hello any black friday
cyber monday deals yes yes yeah
that's all we're staying there yes there
will be yeah maybe like an apple style
3% off they do 5% either yeah yeah no
we'll have some good deals
[Music]
pandas a great stocking stuffer easy to
get started yeah if you really love
someone get them a great panda really
love someone get him an e on Black
Friday yes I've already started like I
went on Amazon and it was like early
Black Friday I'm like November 9th then
they made their own day of it all yeah
cyber monday crazy oh wow okay it's
going around the whole weekend oh but a
note about the fulfillment all orders
ordered after after on - on Monday
nights and ongoing that they will not be
fulfilled until the following Monday
just cuz we're closing fulfillment for
Thanksgiving so actually maybe we can
have a filming don't Tuesday but
regardless your onesie is he here
Wednesday okay so clearly winces yeah
but if you order on like Thursday and
Friday that'll be on fulfill
Monday we're dropping the Thursday
delivery this week yeah yeah we miss you
yeah everything's gonna be at home yeah
enjoying Thanksgiving yeah
it seems like kind of it cool so look
out for that release and all the other
information they save out there with
smoke hey Steve have a this Thanksgiving
my snow peas